Contact

jennyaycock2018@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jenny-aycock-msn-rn-ccrn-42b2a313 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Nursing

Jenny Aycock, MSN, RN, CCRN

Assistant Chief Nursing Officer. Tristar Centennial Hospital Greater Nashville Area, TN

Summary

Experienced Assistant Chief Nursing Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Nursing Administration from Webster University.

Experience

TriStar Centennial Medical Center Assistant Chief Nursing Officer July 2018 - Present (2 years) Nashville, Tennessee

Barnes-Jewish Hospital Interim Director, Emergency Services and Operations July 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Barnes-Jewish Hospital
Clinical Nurse Manager
August 2006 - December 2014 (8 years 5 months)

Providence Alaska Medical Center Critical Care Nurse October 2003 - April 2006 (2 years 7 months)

Barnes-Jewish Hospital Critical Care Nurse May 1993 - July 2003 (10 years 3 months)

Education

Webster University

MSN, Nursing Administration